<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>YANWE</title>
    <link>https://yanwe.win/</link>
    <description>Recent content on YANWE</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://yanwe.win/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yanwe.win/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>13. Huang taiji not very favored xiaozhuang, how to get to the top</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/13.huangtaijibushenchongaidexiaozhuangshiruhedengshangdianfengde/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/13.huangtaijibushenchongaidexiaozhuangshiruhedengshangdianfengde/</guid>
      <description>In the history of the Qing Dynasty, there are two powerful women with whom we are most familiar. One was Empress Dowager Cixi, the birth mother of the Tongzhi Emperor, who held the power of the dynasty for nearly half a century and was the de facto ruler of China during the late Qing Dynasty; the other was Empress Dowager Xiaozhuang, the birth mother of the Shunzhi Emperor, who trained and assisted two generations of emperors, Shunzhi and Kangxi, and was an outstanding politician in the early Qing Dynasty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13. Kako se je Xiaozhuang, ki mu Huang taiji ni bil preveč naklonjen, povzpel </title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/13.huangtaijibushenchongaidexiaozhuangshiruhedengshangdianfengdesl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/13.huangtaijibushenchongaidexiaozhuangshiruhedengshangdianfengdesl/</guid>
      <description>V zgodovini dinastije Qing sta nam najbolj znani dve močni ženski. Ena je bila cesarica vdova Cixi, rodna mati cesarja Tongzhi, ki je skoraj pol stoletja držala vajeti oblasti in bila dejanska vladarica Kitajske v času pozne dinastije Qing; druga je bila cesarica vdova Xiao Zhuang, rodna mati cesarja Shunzhi, ki je vzgajala dve generaciji cesarjev, Shunzhi in Kangxi, in jima pomagala ter bila izjemna državnica v začetku dinastije Qing. Življenje teh dveh žensk je odločilno vplivalo na vzpon in padec dinastije Qing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4.52-year-old Beijing drifters, finally with the right leader</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/52suidelaojingpiaozongsuangenduilehaolingdao/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/52suidelaojingpiaozongsuangenduilehaolingdao/</guid>
      <description>Faced with all the discontents in his life, Gao Shi, at the age of 52, chose to resign and go to Chang&amp;rsquo;an to become a &amp;ldquo;Beijing drifter&amp;rdquo; again.
It took courage to make such a decision. In ancient China, it was not uncommon for people like Tao Yuanming to resign from their posts and return to their fields because they were unhappy with their jobs, but it was rare for people like Gao Shi to resign because he was dissatisfied with his job and rejoin the capital to find a job when he was over half a century old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.8 points to help you achieve cognitive iteration</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/8geyaodianzhunishixianrenzhidiedai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/8geyaodianzhunishixianrenzhidiedai/</guid>
      <description>The promotion path of people in the workplace is usually like this: employee &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; middle management &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; executive &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; VP level &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; entrepreneurial success CEO &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; investor &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; entrepreneurial success CEO &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; investor.
The cognitive ability of investors is considered the top level, because investors need to have enough ability to predict the industry trends and know the future direction, so as to discover companies with potential (high probability of success) for investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.1 The road to face destruction for one user</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/1-geyonghudehuilianzhilu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/1-geyonghudehuilianzhilu/</guid>
      <description>Before starting this book, let me start with a real experience of a user who consulted me, which I have annotated in red
Female, 22 years old, super sensitive Comment 1: A 22 year old girl, why is her skin super sensitive? Did she have sensitive skin since she was born?
I started using skin care products at the age of 17, I used to use Lanzhi exfoliating cream, Hyosungin cleansing products, and Kiehl&amp;rsquo;s white clay, and most importantly, I used to wash my face with a facial cleansing brush every day, which turned my face into this kind of super sensitive skin Comment 2: It turns out that she is not sensitive since childhood, she also found the reason for her sensitive skin - facial cleansing brush, why does a facial cleansing brush cause skin sensitivity?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>38. Should I use anti-aging products after the age of 25?</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/25suihouyaoyongkanglaochanpinma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/25suihouyaoyongkanglaochanpinma/</guid>
      <description>Should I use anti-aging products after the age of 25? &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been told to prevent aging in advance, but do I really need to use anti-aging skin care products after 25? I would like to ask Uncle Mo, what are the safe anti-aging products? As I mentioned in my previous article, since life has entered sexual reproduction, the laws of nature seem to favor the DNA carried in the cells of living beings to be immortalized through the generations, and living beings become a shell, and the meaning of a short life seems to be to pass the DNA, the key object of protection, to the next generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Write in front</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/1.xiezaiqianmian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/1.xiezaiqianmian/</guid>
      <description>Death is often seen as obscure and horrific, and various perceptions have arisen around it, both scientific and superstitious. Forensic pathology, the oldest and most important branch of the forensic profession with its own aura of mystery, has been given more mystery because it focuses on the study of death and corpses.
I first learned about the profession of &amp;ldquo;forensic medicine&amp;rdquo;, in fact, through a film and television drama. At that time, I was still in junior high school, and every night at dinner time, the TV would play a domestic criminal investigation drama, the specific name of the drama now can not remember, only remember that there are a lot of such as &amp;ldquo;extract evidence back to the laboratory to check&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;decent scientific analysis&amp;rdquo; and such unexplained scenes, the main object of examination is the bones, fingerprints, blood, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10. crack Rashomon - in the end who is the driver of the car crushed to death</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/10.pojieluoshengmendaodishuicaishikaicheyasirendesiji/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/10.pojieluoshengmendaodishuicaishikaicheyasirendesiji/</guid>
      <description>We have all seen the crime, kill people and then do their best to conceal the facts of the crime, but who has heard of the race to become a murderer?
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not going to work tomorrow, it&amp;rsquo;s great, it&amp;rsquo;s great! I&amp;rsquo;m not going to work tomorrow, so I can be as lazy as I want! Listening to the rhythm of the music on my phone, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but hum along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Forensic career of the &#39;first&#39; scene</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/2.fayishengyadediyicixianchang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/2.fayishengyadediyicixianchang/</guid>
      <description>But all the things in this world, there is a first time. Some first time is nervous and excited, some first time is surprised and happy, some first time is sad and hard to suppress. In my case, my first contact with forensic work, but with the above-mentioned common feelings are not quite the same.
My first real exposure to forensic work was in the summer after my freshman year. At that time, I contacted the director of forensic medicine of the Public Security Bureau, who would assign us to internship units, through my senior, and asked him to arrange a unit for me to experience forensic work first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. What happens after a high fall</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/3.gaozhuizhihouhuifashengshenme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/3.gaozhuizhihouhuifashengshenme/</guid>
      <description>In the above scene, the deceased died by falling from a height, which is commonly known as &amp;ldquo;jumping&amp;rdquo;. Injuries caused by collision between the human body and the ground or certain objects during the fall are called fall injuries. The form and degree of injury are influenced by the height of the fall, the weight, the presence or absence of obstructions during the fall, the landing method, the landing area, the condition of the ground, and many other factors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. Floating body in the river: how does the forensic pathologist determine the time of death of the deceased?</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/4.hezhongfushifayiruhequedingsizhedesiwangshijian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/4.hezhongfushifayiruhequedingsizhedesiwangshijian/</guid>
      <description>Those with distinctive features and multiple eyewitnesses of the high fall is easier to determine the nature of death, defined as an accident or suicide is a relatively simple matter, after the investigation there is no obvious doubt also generally do not need to be dissected; witnesses are sufficient, the family of the deceased usually will not have any questions. If the body has the kind of plausible damage, the family will see the catch, the forensic work is also more complex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. The body that appeared out of thin air</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/5.pingkongchuxiandeshiti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/5.pingkongchuxiandeshiti/</guid>
      <description>In a furniture city opened a store of gold boss this day is very depressed. Originally this furniture city because of the remote location, closing time early every day, business has been difficult to do, today there is actually a corpse inexplicably appeared. Now it was completely out of business.
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s really bad luck,&amp;rdquo; Mr. Jin whined to us while leading us to the entrance of his store, pointing to the ceiling and saying to us, &amp;ldquo;Look, I was the last one to leave at 6 pm last night, and everything was fine when it closed, and now it&amp;rsquo;s like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6. Relief for the dead, pain for the living</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/6.sizhedejietuoshengzhedetongku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/6.sizhedejietuoshengzhedetongku/</guid>
      <description>Death for the dead themselves, it seems to mean a kind of relief, meaning that the things that happened before they were born are over. But for those who are still alive behind them, this death is likely to be a lifetime of pain and suffering.
Being a forensic scientist is not just about facing corpses, it is also about facing the living. I said in the third &amp;ldquo;Salt Club&amp;rdquo; that</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7. How did the self-hanging lead to death?</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/7.ziyishiruhedaozhisiwangde/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/7.ziyishiruhedaozhisiwangde/</guid>
      <description>In the above case, the deceased died by hanging himself in this way. Death by hanging is caused by using all or part of one&amp;rsquo;s own weight to compress a rope or other similar object around the neck.
The majority of hangings are suicides, or self-hangings, commonly known as &amp;ldquo;hanging&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;hanging&amp;rdquo;. As a &amp;ldquo;star&amp;rdquo; death that often appears in various TV dramas, I believe we are not unfamiliar with hanging, so how exactly does hanging lead to death?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8. Hands struggling to survive</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/8.nuliqiushengdeshuangshou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/8.nuliqiushengdeshuangshou/</guid>
      <description>The actual work of the doctor, the face of the scene of self-hanging is too much. However, the majority of such scenes, by the time the forensic pathologist arrives, have been dead for some time, and the forensic pathologist is faced with a mere corpse.
I have the confidence that I can face any kind of corpse calmly, as to what the corpse actually experienced at the time of death, there are related text descriptions in the textbook, but those descriptions look cold and emotionless, I still have the confidence that I can be strong enough to face such description scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9. Inspiration from The Great Song Judge</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/9.laizidasongtixingguandeqifa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/9.laizidasongtixingguandeqifa/</guid>
      <description>After reading the above heavy case, the reader may have such questions: this time there is video as evidence, that if one is strangled by others, and then hang up disguised as a self-hanging? This is not all wrapped around the neck with a rope to let people die?
Indeed, this kind of rope-like objects wrapped around the neck, through the application of external force, so that the rope-like objects compress the neck death is called strangulation, and hanged very similar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manipulation of the human mind | Japanese intentional murder case: the 64-year-old woman&#39;s borrowed knife to kill 10 people</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/9gezhijirenxingheianmiandizhenshianjian1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/9gezhijirenxingheianmiandizhenshianjian1/</guid>
      <description>If you are an ordinary 64-year-old grandmother, want to effortlessly screw up 7 families, what should you do?
Eat people&amp;rsquo;s money, make the man obsessed with the old and decrepit you and the beautiful wife divorce, even do not even want to work, give you the house property, without your own hands, so that all the people who do not listen to you are killed.
Pretty golden handshake, right?
In reality, can it really be done?</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
