<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>YANWE</title>
    <link>https://yanwe.win/</link>
    <description>Recent content on YANWE</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://yanwe.win/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yanwe.win/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1.1 The road to face destruction for one user</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/1-geyonghudehuilianzhilu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/1-geyonghudehuilianzhilu/</guid>
      <description>Before starting this book, let me start with a real experience of a user who consulted me, which I have annotated in red
Female, 22 years old, super sensitive Comment 1: A 22 year old girl, why is her skin super sensitive? Did she have sensitive skin since she was born?
I started using skin care products at the age of 17, I used to use Lanzhi exfoliating cream, Hyosungin cleansing products, and Kiehl&amp;rsquo;s white clay, and most importantly, I used to wash my face with a facial cleansing brush every day, which turned my face into this kind of super sensitive skin Comment 2: It turns out that she is not sensitive since childhood, she also found the reason for her sensitive skin - facial cleansing brush, why does a facial cleansing brush cause skin sensitivity?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Write in front</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/1.xiezaiqianmian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/1.xiezaiqianmian/</guid>
      <description>Death is often seen as obscure and horrific, and various perceptions have arisen around it, both scientific and superstitious. Forensic pathology, the oldest and most important branch of the forensic profession with its own aura of mystery, has been given more mystery because it focuses on the study of death and corpses.
I first learned about the profession of &amp;ldquo;forensic medicine&amp;rdquo;, in fact, through a film and television drama. At that time, I was still in junior high school, and every night at dinner time, the TV would play a domestic criminal investigation drama, the specific name of the drama now can not remember, only remember that there are a lot of such as &amp;ldquo;extract evidence back to the laboratory to check&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;decent scientific analysis&amp;rdquo; and such unexplained scenes, the main object of examination is the bones, fingerprints, blood, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
