<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ingredient Party Skincare: Building an Affordable Skincare Consumer Program on YANWE</title>
    <link>https://yanwe.win/tags/ingredient-party-skincare-building-an-affordable-skincare-consumer-program/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ingredient Party Skincare: Building an Affordable Skincare Consumer Program on YANWE</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://yanwe.win/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yanwe.win/tags/ingredient-party-skincare-building-an-affordable-skincare-consumer-program/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1.1 The road to face destruction for one user</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/1-geyonghudehuilianzhilu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/1-geyonghudehuilianzhilu/</guid>
      <description>Before starting this book, let me start with a real experience of a user who consulted me, which I have annotated in red
Female, 22 years old, super sensitive Comment 1: A 22 year old girl, why is her skin super sensitive? Did she have sensitive skin since she was born?
I started using skin care products at the age of 17, I used to use Lanzhi exfoliating cream, Hyosungin cleansing products, and Kiehl&amp;rsquo;s white clay, and most importantly, I used to wash my face with a facial cleansing brush every day, which turned my face into this kind of super sensitive skin Comment 2: It turns out that she is not sensitive since childhood, she also found the reason for her sensitive skin - facial cleansing brush, why does a facial cleansing brush cause skin sensitivity?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>38. Should I use anti-aging products after the age of 25?</title>
      <link>https://yanwe.win/post/25suihouyaoyongkanglaochanpinma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanwe.win/post/25suihouyaoyongkanglaochanpinma/</guid>
      <description>Should I use anti-aging products after the age of 25? &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been told to prevent aging in advance, but do I really need to use anti-aging skin care products after 25? I would like to ask Uncle Mo, what are the safe anti-aging products? As I mentioned in my previous article, since life has entered sexual reproduction, the laws of nature seem to favor the DNA carried in the cells of living beings to be immortalized through the generations, and living beings become a shell, and the meaning of a short life seems to be to pass the DNA, the key object of protection, to the next generation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
