<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on YANWE</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/post/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on YANWE</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://yanwe.win/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Chapter 1: Model Couple | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00001/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00001/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 1: Model Couple
On the day of the beginning of spring, Xiangcheng experienced a substantial snowfall, and the biting wind stung the face, making it painfully cold.
Exiting the art gallery, Gu Shisheng opened his phone only to find a message from his husband.
&amp;ldquo;[It&amp;rsquo;s snowing, and it&amp;rsquo;s cold. I asked Uncle Zhou to pick you up. The project will end in two days, and we can go to Nancheng to see the sea together.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 10: Gu Shisheng Is Someone Else&#39;s Wife | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00010/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00010/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 10: Gu Shisheng Is Someone Else&amp;rsquo;s Wife
The winter in Xiangcheng felt endless, probably extending directly over the entire spring. The outside sky lacked sunlight, appearing gloomy and dark.
Wu Nian handed a cup of coffee to Gu Shisheng in the office, and her eyes caught the slightly yellowed gardenia flowers on the desk.
&amp;ldquo;What a pity. I wonder where Jiang Zhaoxi went.&amp;rdquo; He had always been the one taking care of these flowers.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 11: Is the Same Scene Stimulating? | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00011/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00011/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 11: Is the Same Scene Stimulating?
Not far from Nancheng, but by the time they arrived, two hours had passed.
The hotel they checked into was situated by the sea, and the floor-to-ceiling windows provided a perfect view of the most beautiful scenery. The moonlit sea seemed to be draped in a hazy veil, reflecting millions of stars, making it difficult to distinguish between reality and illusion.
&amp;ldquo;Wife, happy birthday,&amp;rdquo; Lu Siyi said, smiling.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 12: Promised Happiness for Your Remaining Years | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00012/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00012/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 12: Promised Happiness for Your Remaining Years
In the middle of the night, Gu Shisheng felt movement beside him, and the man embraced him from behind. Gu Shisheng wasn&amp;rsquo;t asleep; he had passed many sleepless nights, but tonight was an exception.
It couldn&amp;rsquo;t entirely be blamed on Lu Siyi. The outside temptations were plentiful, and Gu Shisheng wasn&amp;rsquo;t the best or the most unique. After experiencing it, he genuinely felt that each beauty outside had its own charm, like a spice adding excitement to the dull and monotonous daily life.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 13: Where Were You Last Night? | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00013/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00013/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 13: Where Were You Last Night?
Gu Shisheng pushed away the quite drunk Shen Qinghe, his eyes showing no ripples as he asked the bewildered youth, &amp;ldquo;What do you love about me?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;What?&amp;rdquo; Shen Qinghe was a bit unclear.
&amp;ldquo;Do you love my appearance? Or do you love that I helped you in your most difficult times? Or is it because I now present myself as refined and graceful?&amp;rdquo; Gu Shisheng seemed genuinely puzzled.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 14: How Can I Not Fall in Love with Young Lu Siyi | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00014/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00014/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 14: How Can I Not Fall in Love with Young Lu Siyi
&amp;ldquo;Didn&amp;rsquo;t you say you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get angry before?&amp;rdquo; Gu Shisheng helped Lu Siyi take off his coat, a gentle smile on his face. &amp;ldquo;For such things, it&amp;rsquo;s not worth it.&amp;rdquo;
Lu Siyi turned around, embracing Gu Shisheng. &amp;ldquo;Scare him a bit, so he won&amp;rsquo;t cause trouble these two days.&amp;rdquo;
Gu Shisheng understood, smiling somewhat helplessly. &amp;ldquo;You, really!&amp;rdquo;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 15: A Face Resembling Gu Shisheng | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00015/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00015/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 15: A Face Resembling Gu Shisheng
Gu Shisheng pushed open the door. The servant had prepared some refreshments for him.
&amp;ldquo;Mr. Lu said you should have something to eat first; the banquet can wait.&amp;rdquo;
Everyone in the Lu family envied Gu Shisheng. A poor child from a rural family had the fortune and luck to marry Lu Siyi. Moreover, he received the supreme favor of Mr. Lu. What great luck and blessing!</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 16: Those Lovers That Captivate Gu Shisheng | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00016/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00016/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 16: Those Lovers That Captivate Gu Shisheng
Gu Shisheng wasn&amp;rsquo;t happy. When he stared at Lu Siyi with his misty blue eyes, it didn&amp;rsquo;t seem like anger, but more like grievance.
So, in the end, Lu Siyi always had to compromise.
But this time was different.
Lu Siyi reached out and pinched Gu Shisheng&amp;rsquo;s nose, smiling helplessly. &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ve calculated that I won&amp;rsquo;t do anything to you, right? Let&amp;rsquo;s go; I&amp;rsquo;ll take you upstairs to rest.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 17: Taking Advantage of Someone&#39;s Misfortune, Shameless Act | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00017/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00017/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 17: Taking Advantage of Someone&amp;rsquo;s Misfortune, Shameless Act
Under the influence of alcohol, Gu Shisheng found a pavilion to sit in. The Lu family estate was vast, with many courtyards and pavilions, exuding a classical and aristocratic charm. Bamboo was planted in the courtyard, and under the moonlight, it created a faint and elegant scene. The sound of a few insects in the woods disturbed a pair of moths, causing them to flutter over the surface of the lake by the pavilion, creating ripples.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 18: Jiang Chaoxi&#39;s Defeat in Youth | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00018/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00018/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 18: Jiang Chaoxi&amp;rsquo;s Defeat in Youth
Blood splattered on his face, reddening Jiang Chaoxi&amp;rsquo;s eyes. He resembled a fierce wolf, frightening everyone around him. Shouts and screams filled the air, chaos ensued. People remembered that Young Master Jiang had been abroad for many years, but they forgot that Jiang Young Master and the second son of the Ye family should never stand in the same place.
The two had grown up together but never got along.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 2: All Alone | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00002/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00002/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 2: All Alone
The airport bustled with people, and a tall man with a graceful figure attracted numerous gazes as soon as he appeared. His face was perfectly rugged, devoid of a smile, and his thin lips carried a hint of coolness. He looked down at the watch on his wrist.
When the man answered the phone, his entire demeanor softened, and an aura of tenderness enveloped him. People could see the affection in his eyes.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 3: Monotonous Accumulation | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00003/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00003/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 3: Monotonous Accumulation
In the kitchen, Lu Siyi rolled up his sleeves and chopped vegetables. Gu Shisheng leaned against the door frame, watching the man from top to bottom. His gaze lingered for a moment on the red mark on the man&amp;rsquo;s neck before gently shifting his focus.
Who would have thought that Lu Siyi, the calm and composed negotiator at the conference table, would be at home wearing an apron and cooking?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 4: His Kindness, Given to Only One | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00004/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00004/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 4: His Kindness, Given to Only One
Lu Siyi left first.
Gu Shisheng went to a nearby café alone for a while, then took the circular bus. Somehow, he ended up at the entrance of their high school.
Gu Shisheng got off the bus there.
Since it was during the holidays, the school entrance was deserted. Unable to enter, he stood outside, took a few glances, circled around, and found a small eatery to sit down, ordering a bowl of rice noodles.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 5: The Land of the Well-Behaved Lu Siyi | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00005/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00005/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 5: The Land of the Well-Behaved Lu Siyi
That bowl of rice noodles prevented Gu Shisheng from going home.
Regarding the hospital visit, Gu Shisheng hadn&amp;rsquo;t told anyone. It was during the midnight IV infusion when Gu Shisheng saw the message from Lu Siyi, saying he had work and wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be coming back that night.
He opened his phone, thinking of replying but hesitated, considering that it might be inconvenient at this time.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 6: Attractive and Easily Deceived | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00006/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00006/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 6: Attractive and Easily Deceived
After receiving morning intravenous therapy, Gu Shisheng returned to the gallery in the afternoon. The gallery was located in the best area of Jinjiang, occupying the entire floor of the 20th floor of the Jin Yu Building.
The room with the best lighting inside was Gu Shisheng&amp;rsquo;s studio. He moved the drawing board, secured the drawing paper, and, with his head lowered, suddenly didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to put the brush to paper, staring blankly out the window.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 7: Weariness After the Passage of Time | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00007/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00007/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 7: Weariness After the Passage of Time
Several young people, no longer as nervous as before, became more talkative.
Wu Nian and Zheng Sui eagerly sought advice from Gu Shisheng, while Jiang Chaoxi set aside to watch his wife.
His wife&amp;rsquo;s posture with the pen was really pleasing, her voice was pleasant, and she looked even more beautiful when she smiled. What was going on with these two? Was the workplace a place to ask about painting?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 8: The Final Hurt to Gu Shisheng | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00008/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00008/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 8: The Final Hurt to Gu Shisheng
Lu Siyi took two days off from work to accompany Gu Shisheng. If it weren&amp;rsquo;t for Gu Shisheng insisting that Lu Siyi go back to work on the third day, Lu Siyi would have brought his work to the hospital.
&amp;ldquo;I need to take care of myself even when you&amp;rsquo;re not around. Qin Auntie will bring lunch at noon. Remember to video call me when you&amp;rsquo;re eating.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Chapter 9: Sorry, I&#39;m Married | Seven Years into Marriage, I Cheated</title>
        <link>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00009/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://yanwe.win/en/syimic00009/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 9: Sorry, I&amp;rsquo;m Married
Gu Shisheng hadn&amp;rsquo;t eaten such childish food in a long time, but it was genuinely sweet, both sour and sweet, flooding his brain. He didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to speak for a moment.
&amp;ldquo;Did you put the flowers there?&amp;rdquo;
Gu Shisheng didn&amp;rsquo;t keep flowers because he wasn&amp;rsquo;t good at it; the flowers he kept tended to die quickly, and when they did, Gu Shisheng would blame himself.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
